You can't run away from it, because you have already seen the light.
Oh my gosh, the girls are going to flock to him like geese.
Hey, cut it out.
What would you do if this gets you a bunch of new fans?
Like that would ever happen to me.
You can never be sure.
Think you got what it takes when the time comes?
Sorry, there's someone else I like.
Huh? What? What are you talking about?
She wasn't there, was she?
Sorry, there's someone else I like a lot.
Let's practice. I like you, Ichikawa.
Come on.
Yamada... likes me?
Huh?
Even if she does, that doesn't mean anything's changed.
It actually means I gotta be more careful.
Unlike when someone doesn't like you at all,
messing up when someone actually does ruins things for good.
Watch yourself.
Ah, just stop it!
You can't go getting creepy.
Hey, uh...
Oh, yeah.
The basketball club is gonna go out to do karaoke with everyone who just graduated.
You coming?
What? Of course I'll come!
Hard to find the right timing to talk.
Not much I can do about that.
Karaoke, huh?
Not the sort of thing I ever do.
Yamada's coming too!
No way, really?
Yeah!
It's the basketball club!
The B-Ball guys are going too?
Whoever's going straight there, follow me!
Don't be creepy like this!
Yay!
Okay, Yamada, you're up next.
Are you still eating?
No worries, we'll do another toast.
Everyone pick up your glasses.
Then here's to Kobayashi's amazing three-point shot.
Hooray!
Okay, Yamada, now you.
She's always eating!
There they are.
Closer than I thought!
Better watch myself.
Who wanted melon soda again?
Huh?
Isn't that...
That's the kid who gave the farewell speech.
Yeah, you're right.
Everyone has been talking about you.
Did you ad-lib that whole thing?
Hey, come on, sing with us!
Go on already.
Ichikawa!
Yeah!
What are you doing here?
Huh?
I'm so dead.
I'm just some creep stalking her in her fun little party.
I'm...
Why are you here?
Weren't you having fun?
I was, but...
I quit the club early on.
So celebrating with them like that...
Kind of feels like I'm out of place, you know?
What are you doing here in a place like karaoke?
Should I pretend it's all a coincidence?
No, me coming to karaoke alone is weird too!
Huh?
Did you maybe...
Follow me here?
Huh?
What?
No, I, uh...
I, um...
Wasn't worried about you or anything.
Ah!
Ichikawa...
Huh?
Did you maybe hear me say I liked someone when we were in the nurse's office the other day?
Well...
Now?
Well, it's...
Just...
When I was saying it out loud...
My heart started racing like crazy.
Kind of...
Like I was realizing it all over again.
And so I got worked up!
Which had me acting like a weirdo all day long.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
It doesn't make sense, huh?
But that's all it is, so you don't need to worry about it at all.
I mean...
That's not it.
I wasn't worried about that.
Huh?
Confront yourself.
And how creepy you are!
I didn't like seeing you go out with the b-ball guys.
I got all worked up, so...
Huh?
Sorry.
How did...
This even happen?!
Thank you.
Yesterday was such a mess.
That's those basketball kids for you, extroverts.
They know no mercy.
Uh, let's give it up for Ichikawa's great speech and singing voice.
Yeah, hooray!
I mean, I guess they weren't all that bad.
Ah, Ichikawa!
Glad I found you.
Hm? What's up?
Well, it's just that there's something I want to talk to you about.
W-what's going on?
What the-
You were in here?
Oh, you too, Yamada.
Wait, Sweet Paradise? Count me super in!
That's a relief.
Oh, and also, would it be alright if Kanzuki joins in with us?
Wait, you mean like-
In perfect sync.
Uh, but, um, wouldn't we just be in the way between you and Kanzuki?
If it's like a date and all.
Well, um, I don't really get why, but he was the one who suggested that you two come along with us.
Hm?
Why would he?
Not sure.
But truth is, the two of us go out alone plenty already.
When did that guy start?
Oh, okay.
Well, just so we're clear and all.
Are the two of you going out as a couple?
No, not at all.
You go out together all the time, but you're still not going out as a couple?
What?
Hm.
I don't mind if you don't.
It sounds like it'll be fun.
If she gets in the way too much, you can just ditch her.
Huh?
Oh.
Well, you're coming too.
Huh?
I mean, this Saturday is March 14th, you get it?
White day!
I'll go if I can.
That means you will!
Does it really?
But...
She says she'll come.
Oh, that's great to hear.
And you too.
Huh?
Does that make this...
A double date?
This'll be fun.
Today's the big day.
Here as fast as always.
Ichikawa!
Ugh.
Not in her uniform.
Took the same train, huh?
It's still a little early, so I thought I might be waiting alone.
Oh, yeah.
I thought I'd get some shopping in beforehand.
For white day, you mean?
Um, what?
No.
Nothing like that, really.
Truth is, I still can't make up my mind about it.
Let me see if I can help.
This is Yamada we're talking about.
Exactly.
I knew it.
How does she know?
I guess it's fine if it's just her.
The more I think about it, the more I can't decide.
I'm so lost about it.
All I can find online is what not to get.
I know what you mean.
I can't promise I'll be a huge help or anything.
But wanna go shopping together?
Huh?
Wait, but can we...
We're here.
Is this whole situation really okay?
You probably can't go wrong with food as a gift.
It's just, she eats nothing but delicious stuff all the time.
Yeah, that's true.
And it'd be so weird if I made something for her, right?
She would probably think I poisoned it.
Seriously?
I wouldn't say that.
What was it that she gave you on Valentine's Day?
Um, like a chocolate muffin or something?
A handmade one?
Yeah.
What did you think?
What?
I mean, well I was pretty happy.
But there's a difference between something she makes and something I make.
You think so?
Wouldn't buying jewelry be super weird and personal?
Ugh.
People do have their preferences.
Maybe I'll just give her a catalog to choose from.
That's a little impersonal, don't you think?
Ugh.
I'm being pretty negative, aren't I?
Sorry.
I get it.
I'm kinda the same way.
Guess we're a bit similar in that way, aren't we?
Huh?
What's that mean?
She's scaring me!
Ugh.
How about a hat?
A fluffy hat for Yamada.
Ichika!
Oh yeah!
That would look cute!
Huh?
What?
Oh yeah!
That would totally look cute!
You do look super adorable!
Right?
Is this...
Chelsea?
Huh?
Oh dude, it's not like what you're thinking at all!
Wait a minute...
Why is he here early?
Yamada, you look super cute as always, too!
Isn't that right?
Huh?
She looks real cute!
Right?
Yeah!
Totally!
Hara!
Well, it's almost time to eat!
So we should all get going then!
This is dumb!
This is dumb.
Everyone's got things all mixed up.
Think I'll take one of these too.
I can't decide.
Hara's so adorable, isn't she?
Sure thing.
Don't you go agreeing!
Huh?
You should say, I bet she turns you on.
Now say it back to me.
Hara really turns you on, huh?
Quit looking at her like that, creep.
What?
Better.
Can I leave yet?
This is ridiculous.
I wasn't saying Hara looked cute.
Sorry for the wait.
Hara, I'm paying for this, so eat all the dessert you want.
You are?
No, no, it's fine.
I'm actually pretty full.
Like a rumble from the Earth itself.
She's always like this.
That's why I invited Yamada.
I just figured if she was here, then Hara would feel free
to eat as much food as she liked.
Oh, yeah.
You're perfect enough just the way you are.
Nothing's better.
Did you actually just say that?
Crazy!
Yeah, I mean, she is, right?
Don't be too impressed.
He says it about once a minute.
Seriously?
Amazing!
That's nice.
Here, have some fries.
Eat up!
No, thank you.
Why?
I mean it.
You're perfect the way you-
Drop it.
Doing what you're doing is just forcing your own opinion.
If she doesn't want to be the way she is, then leave her be.
You don't get to stop her like that from wanting to change.
I'm here because I want to change, too.
I'm sorry, you're right.
But honestly, I really wouldn't feel any different whether she was chubby or skinny as a rail.
I like how happy you look when you're eating, so it doesn't matter at all to me.
Here, this is for you.
What did you give her?
Oh, it's so cute!
A set of cutlery!
Fine, if you're going to make a big deal, maybe I'll eat some more.
This is so delicious!
What?
Yamada picked that out?
She did.
She really knows how to shop for people.
I showed up early but was having a hard time picking something out.
There were too many choices for me to look at.
Then she just happened by and helped.
She's a lot easier to talk to than she looks.
Don't talk to her.
That big appetite's nice, too.
Don't look at her!
Hmm?
Don't go shopping alone with her!
He definitely has skills I don't.
Oh, yeah, right!
Cause she's kind of famous and all.
Oh, man!
Not because of that!
Um...
Cause Yamada is mine!
No!
I mean, um...
Just you're mindful!
Of...
Uh...
What'd you eat?
But you sure had lots of curry one time!
Uh...
This isn't about what Kanzaki has.
It's about what I lack.
As a man.
So you mean that, huh?
You have a thing for her.
Hilarious, right?
Me and Yamada....
We ended up hearing about you taste pastries, huh?
You ended up hearing about her pastries.
I'm not cut out for her.
You really think that?
Everyone always says you're a pretty good guy.
Your speech was a banger, too.
It was like you'd forgotten to be not in the pastries, huh?
It was like you'd felt pain, I'd have to be on the pastries.
You really think that? Everyone always says you're a pretty good guy. Your speech was a banger, too. It was like you'd found yourself up there. Pretty cool. So who knows, man. You might be a good fit for her.
Well, then, what's going on with you and Hara? Shouldn't you ask her out already?
I already did ask her.
What? Is he talking about earlier?
I mean, she just never takes me seriously. At the rate things are going, we're going to be stuck in this will-they-won't-they limbo until we just wind up as friends with benefits, you know?
Though, guess that's fine, too.
This dude's seriously got a screw or two loose up in there.
Uh-oh. Looks like Yamada got lost in the crowd.
Could you be more obvious, Hara?
Um, let's split up and look for her. We'll go check this way, so you go that way and give it a good, thorough look.
Wait, but shouldn't we stick together?
Just do what I say!
That was a bit much.
What was?
I mean...
I mean, just because you spend a lot of time alone with someone you really like doesn't mean you don't want to keep doing it again and again.
What?
Oh, no! I mean, Hara and Kanzuki!
Uh, right, of course.
So, um, what do you want to do now?
Let's go home.
Okay.
This is the right choice. Forget about this.
I can't stop comparing myself to people.
The smallest stuff sets me off, and then I start hating myself for it.
Sorry I'm such a pain.
Shut up!
Have you forgotten already?
Who trusts in you more than anyone else?
You have something important in your bag?
Yeah.
Yamada.
What is it?
When we get to the station, do you have a minute?
Hara and Kanzuki are sharing a booth at a Met Cafe!
Those two are acting so grown up, don't you think?
Uh-huh.
But...
Honestly, I kind of like this more.
It's like you're sharing a booth at a net cafe.
Those two are acting so grown up, don't you think?
Uh-huh.
But, honestly, I kind of like this more.
Now I see it.
It's the same for her.
Yamada also had to be brave on Valentine's Day.
Comparing myself to others and getting jealous is just me protecting me.
Don't be an idiot.
Quit looking at anything else.
Kiyotaro Ichikawa.
All you need is to think about her.
Here.
A muffin! Just like the one I gave.
Bet you're disappointed.
No way! Not one bit. Did you make this one?
I was there when you all learned how, remember?
Call it foreshadowing or something.
I bet you're already full today, so...
Huh?
Oh, thank you.
One bite at a time!
Oh!
Um...
Sorry, I'm just so happy.
I'm...
Ugh...
Giving jewelry is definitely super weird.
Like Hara said, people have their own preferences.
Uh...
Agh...
Hey.
Put it on.
How's it look?
It's so cute. I could die.
I like her.
I do. I really do.
Wait.
Why am I crying so much?
These are different from those tears before.
This is the smallest, most important step forward.
This is our way.